Doris Holmes Eyges Journals MS079
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Doris Holmes Eyges Journals
1957 -- 2000
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Eyges, Doris Holmes
MS079
2.4 Linear Feet 2 boxes
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains Doris Holmes Eyges' daily journals in a series of bound volumes, from 1957 until 2000. Doris Holmes Eyges was a poet and taught courses at Tufts University and Wellesley College. She was married to the poet John Holmes until his death in 1962. She married Leonard Eyges in 1969.
Related Materials
MS007 John A. Holmes papers. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Biographical / Historical
Poet and widow of John Holmes. Lecturer Emeritus at Wellesley College.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Greater Boston arts
- Journals, 1957 -- 2000; MS079.001; 2.4 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Doris Holmes Eyges' daily journals in bound volumes from 1957 to 2000.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation.
  - Journal, 1957-04-07 -- 1958-04-12; MS079.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1958-04-20 -- 1958-12-29; MS079.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1959-01-13 -- 1959-04-06; MS079.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1959-04-27 -- 1959-09-04; MS079.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1959-09-04 -- 1960-05-18; MS079.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1960-05-22 -- 1960-11-01; MS079.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1960-11-09 -- 1961-06-24; MS079.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1961-06-25 -- 1962-05-08; MS079.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1962-04-22 -- 1963-01-21; MS079.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1963-01-27 -- 1963-06-28; MS079.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1963-07-06 -- 1963-09-05; MS079.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1963-10-07 -- 1963-11-26; MS079.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1964-11-30 -- 1965-10-29; MS079.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1965-11-03 -- 1966-11-03; MS079.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1966-11-04 -- 1967-05-30; MS079.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1967-05-30 -- 1968-04-13; MS079.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1968-04-13 -- 1969-01-02; MS079.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1969-01-02 -- 1969-11-09; MS079.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1969-11-11 -- 1971-03-01; MS079.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1971-02-10 -- 1972-03-13; MS079.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1972-05-02 -- 1973-01-05; MS079.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1973-01-08 -- 1973-07-11; MS079.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1973-07-13 -- 1974-08-11; MS079.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1974-01-23 -- 1974-09-20; MS079.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Journal, 1974-09-20 -- 1975-04-19; MS079.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1975-04-20 -- 1976-02-03; MS079.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1976-02-05 -- 1976-08-23; MS079.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1976-09-05 -- 1977-09-02; MS079.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1977-07-21 -- 1977-08-12; MS079.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1977-09-06 -- 1978-06-13; MS079.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1978-06-14 -- 1979-05-19; MS079.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1979-05-20 -- 1980-06-02; MS079.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1980-06-07 -- 1981-08-21; MS079.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1981-08-23 -- 1982-01-09; MS079.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1982-01-09 -- 1983-01-11; MS079.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1983-01-11 -- 1984-05-22; MS079.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1984-05-25 -- 1985-04-22; MS079.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1985-04-29 -- 1986-07-06; MS079.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1986-07-07 -- 1987-03-09; MS079.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1987-03-10 -- 1988-02-20; MS079.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1988-02-20 -- 1988-12-21; MS079.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1988-12-28 -- 1990-05-20; MS079.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1990-06-05 -- 1991-08-06; MS079.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1991-08-14 -- 1993-01-03; MS079.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1993-01-04 -- 1994-06-29; MS079.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1994-07-05 -- 1996-05-16; MS079.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1996-05-13 -- 1998-05-11; MS079.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Journal, 1998-05-13 -- 2000-02-11; MS079.001.002.00024 (Box 2)